Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Glossies: Products, Special Boxes, Records, 1979-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Montor Records Graphics, 1982-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Children Under Apartheid, A portable photographic exhibition produced by International Defence and Aid Fund for Southern Africa in co-operation with United Nations Centre Against Apartheid for International Year of the Child, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- [Trade For Peace Inc. Photos], 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Africa, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- [Illustrated published materials most likely used for photograph research], 1967-1988; 2.0 folders (Box 16, Folder 1,2)
- MP Records, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Book Covers, 1975-1982; 2.0 folders (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
- Marketplace Veloxes, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Book Covers, 1974-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Marketplace Copies, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Product Art MP, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
- MP Posters, 1975-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
- [Artist Renditions], 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Feggo, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Christopher Temptander, 1973-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
- MP: Art for Special Boxes Section, 1979-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
- [Ethiopian Negatives], 1976-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
- [Libya Negatives], Apr. 4,1980-Apr. 4, 1980; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
- [Anti-Nuclear Negatives], undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
- [Negatives-Elias Avoub and Harlem Protest of Atlanta Murders], 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
- [Demonstration in front of British Consulate and Anti-Klan Conference], 1980-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
- [Young Americans for Freedom Negatives], undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Manila Folder titled "Bob" contains unidentifiable negatives, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Military, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 22)
- [Anti-Imperialist Contingent Negatives], undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Women In Army, 1966-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Agent Orange, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 25)
- [Negatives-University Club El Salvador and Guardian Sustainer Party], 1980-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 26)
- [Negatives-Sustainer Party and Demo NYC Fort Apache: The Bronx Movie], 1980-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 27)
- [Eritrea, EPLF Soldiers and "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" An Anti-Inflation Comedy], 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 28)
- [Historical Temperence Movement, EPLF and Eritrea], 1975-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 29)
- [Board of Education and Integration Demonstrations], 1963-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Anti-Apartheid Rally D.C., 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 31)
- [Labor, Immigration, Women Demonstrations], 1979-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 32)
- [Demonstrations-Iranian Students, Fort Apache, El Salvador, Solidarity Day Etc.], 1979-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 33)
- [Cutbacks Protests, Memorial March Gene Viernes, Ethiopia, Etc.], 1976-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 34)
- [Demonstrations-Anti-Racism Violence], 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 35)
- [Miscellaneous Protests and Demonstrations], 1954-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 36)
- [Color Slides], 1973-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 37)
- [Graphics Maps], 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 38)
- [Cartoons], 1984-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Military-Industrial Complex, 1968-; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Documentary of Vietnam, 1940-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Nixon Era Graphics, 1968-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Cambodia Soldiers, 1970-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 16, Folder 43-44)
- Kampuchea, 1970-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
- Phnom Penh, 1970-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Vietnam – Mugs, 1976-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Vietnam – Militia/ Army, 1975-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Vietnam – Medicine, 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Vietnam – Education, 1975-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Vietnam – Scars of War, 1973-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Vietnam – Elections, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Vietnam – Industry, 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Vietnam/Kampuchea/China Changes in Economy, 1977-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Vietnam – Agriculture Forestry/ Dairy/ Fishing, 1971-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Vietnam – Scenes, 1976-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Vietnam – Art/Culture, 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Reconstruction – General, 1975-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Vietnam – Children, 1975-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Vietnam – Sports, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Vietnamese in U.S., 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Vietnam – National Celebrations Congresses, Meetings, etc., 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Vietnam – Liberation, 1973-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Women, 1976-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Vietnam, 1961-1976; 3.0 folders (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
- Foreign Politicians, 1966-1973; 2.0 folders (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
- The G.I. in Action before the Vietnamese Liberation, 1962-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 27)
- South Vietnamese Politicians During U.S. Aggressive War, 1957-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 28)
- The U.S. Air-bases in South Vietnam, 1963-1973; 2.0 folders (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
- The U.S. Weapons in South Vietnam, 1967-1972; 2.0 folders (Box 17, Folder 31-32)
- Women, 1966-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Vietnam, 1954-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- Way of Life S. Vietnam, 1962-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Medical Care S. Vietnam, 1966-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Anti-U.S. Air Graft During War, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Agriculture During War, 1970-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Children During War, 1967-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Construction and Way of Life During War, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Culture During War, 1971-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Industry During War, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Medical Care During War, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Women During War, 1967-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Politic During War, 1969-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 13)
- N. Vietnamese Politician During War, 1966-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
- Uncle Ho Chi Minh, 1950-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 16)
- U.S. Prisoner in N. Vietnam During War, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Education During War, 1969-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Education Post War, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Military Post War, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Children Post War, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Medical Care Post War, 1975-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Industry Post War, 1975-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Culture Post War, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Reconstruction Post War, 1975-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Army of Vietnam During War, 1949-1974; 2.0 folders (Box 18, Folder 26-27)
- All About Viet-Gong, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Deconstruction Defoliation During War, 1963-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 18, Folder 29-30)
- Vietnam Photos, 1972-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
- Politics Post War, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Yen Truong Co-operative, 1971-; 1.0 folder (Box 18, Folder 34)
- A, 1955-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Muhammed Ali, 1968-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Isabel Allende, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Salvador Allende, 1964-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Herbert Aptheker, 1963-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Yasser Arafat, 1974-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 6)
- James Aronson, 1949-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Ralph Abernathy, 1968-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Bella Abzug, 1971-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Spiro Agnew, 1970-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 10)
- B, 1954-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
- B Politician G.O.P./Dems/Civil Rights Activists, etc., 1966-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Joan Baez, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Cedric Belfrage, 1953-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Daniel Berrigan & Phil Berrigan, 1968-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Maurice Bishop, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Ann & Carl Braden, 1958-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Leonid Breezhnez, 1971-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 19)
- H. Rap Brown, 1967-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Simone de Bouvoir, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Burchett Booklet, 1960-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Wilfred Burchett, 1964-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Manny Bloch – Rosenberg’s Lawyer, 1953-1954; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Political C, 1967-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous C, 1964-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Rubin Carter, 1975-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Stokely Carmichael, 1966-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Lt. William Calley (and friends), 1969-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 29)
- George Washington Carver, 1937-1948; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Fidel Castro, 1959-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Chiang Ching (Mao’s wife), undated; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Angela Davis, 1970-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Misc. D, 1950-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Richard J. Daley, 1970-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Ron Dellums, 1971-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Barbara Dane, 1967-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Ben Davis, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Rennie Davis, 1969-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Clifton DeBerry, 1964-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 40)
- E.V. Debs, 1980-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Dave Dellinger, 1969-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Isaac Deutscher, 1958-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Dinkins, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Cuba Usvaido Dorticos, 1959-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 45)
- William Douglas, 1964-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Duarte, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 47)
- W.E.B. Dubois, 1948-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Bob Dylan, 1967-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Mike Dukakis, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous E, 1964-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Cyrus Eaton, 1958-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Dr. Kenneth Edelin, 1974-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Albert Einstein, 1946-1961; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Charles Evers, 1968-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 55)
- W, 1962-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 56)
- Waldheim, 1971-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 57)
- Wallace, 1972-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Bill Walton, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Harold Washington See also Illinois, 1983-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 60)
- General William Westmoreland, 1965-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 61)
- Wilson, Brian, 1990-; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Robert F Williams, 1961-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 63)
- Woodcock, 1970-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 64)
- X, 1964-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Y, 1957-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 66)
- Andy Young – U.N., 1970-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 67)
- Yabionski Case, 1969-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 68)
- Cedric Belfrage Memorial, Nov. 12, 1990; 1.0 folder (Box 19, Folder 69)
- Z, 1963-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Military, U.S., 1959-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 2)
- U.S. Spy Planes Downed in USSR (Espionage), 1960-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Troops & Maneuvers (Armed Forces), 1962-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Powers – U-2 Incident (Espionage), 1960-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 5)
- G.I. Civilian Demonstrations – On & Off Base (Armed Forces), 1967-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Generals & Admirals, 1948-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Atom Radiation, 1960-1964; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Missiles, 1957-1968; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Weaponry – Aircraft (Armed Forces), 1964-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Weaponry – Ships, Carriers, Destroyers (Armed Forces), 1952-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Satellites-Science and Technology, 1962-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 12)
- NASA, 1961-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Security/Surveillance, 1957-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Joint Chiefs of Staff – (past & present), 1967-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Defense Dept., 1962-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Defections, 1960-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Various Armed Forces Crimes & Court-martials, 1967-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Gen. George C. Marshall, 1947-1953; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 19)
- G.I.s & Army, 1967-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Weaponry – Atomic (Armed Forces), 1945-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Alleged U.S. Spys [sic] (Espionage), 1959-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Alleged Spys [sic] for Communist Countries (Espionage), 1960-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 23)
- GI Movement, 1966-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Draft Resistance, 1968-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Pueblo Incident (Espionage), 1969-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 26)
- V.E. Day, 1945-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Concentration Camps, 1945-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Children Of War, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Iran/Contra Scandal Hearings, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Left Confabs, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Robots, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Rock-N-Roll, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Sanctuary, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Sexuality, 1983-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Social Security, 1935-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Socialist Workers Party, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Space/Star Wars, 1971-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Sports, 1981-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 39)
- “Spying” FBI, CIA, etc., 1971-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 40)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- AK, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 41)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- AZ, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 42)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- CO, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 43)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- CA, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 44)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- D.C, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 45)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- DE, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 46)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- FL, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 47)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IA, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 48)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- ID, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 49)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IL, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 50)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IN, 1986-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 51)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- LA, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 52)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MA, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 53)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MI, 1984-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 54)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MN, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 55)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MISCELLANEOUS, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 56)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MT, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 57)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- NH, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 58)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- SD, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 59)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- TN, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 60)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- TX, 1982-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 61)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- VA, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 62)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- VT, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 63)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- WI, 1983-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Teaching, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Technology & Science, 1959-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Tenants Rights, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 67)
- Transit, 1983-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Unemployment/Graphics, 1968-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 69)
- Women, 1973-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Weaponry –Tanks, Artillery (Armed Forces), 1956-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Welfare, 1968-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 72)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians /NY, 1984-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Veterans/ POWs, 1985-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 74)
- Utilities & Public Workers, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Watsonville Strike, CA 1985, 1986 Peter Maiden Photos, 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 76)
- War Toys, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Welfare Workers, 1965-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 78)
- Woolworth, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 79)
- WBAI, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 80)
- Women in Sports, 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 81)
- Temp Boorfile, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 82)
- Workers – Miscellaneous, 1947-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 83)
- Women in Workforce, 1971-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 84)
- US/USSR, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 20, Folder 85)
- Aircraft Workers, 1945-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Auto Workers, 1952-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
- AFL-CIO, 1953-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Automation-Technology, 1957-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Boeing Strike, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Clerical Workers, 1961-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Clerical Workers/ Yale Strike, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Communication Workers Telephone – TV – Radio, 1952-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Construction Workers, 1964-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Eastern, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Electrical Workers, 1948-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Farmworkers Migrant Sharecroppers, 1956-1982; 2.0 folders (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
- United Farmworkers, 1941-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 15)
- UFW Cesar Chavez, 1966-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 16)
- United Farmworkers, 1966-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 17)
- UFW – Support Demonstrations, 1965-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Garment & Textile, 1952-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Government Workers, 1953-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Hormel P-N (Meatpackers), 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Hospital Workers, 1965-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Hospital Workers (1199), 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Hotel Workers, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Steel Workers, 1925-1986; 5.0 folders (Box 21, Folder 25-29)
- Airline Strikes, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1936-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 1)
- A.I.D.S., 1985-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Alliance for Cultural Democracy Conference, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Animal Rights/Animal Cruelty, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Arms Tacks & Arms Control, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Asbestos, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Auto Industry, 1970-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Aviation Industry – see also Military Hardware, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Asian Americans, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Tawana Brawley Case, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Black Struggle – Freedom Ride 1986, 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Black Capitalism, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 12)
- U.S. Blacks 3rd World Solidarity, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Black Leaders Meet @ Southern, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Leaders – Black, 1963-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Black Personalities, 1967-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Black History/Personalities, 1948-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Black Struggles, 1963-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Black Struggle (N.Y. 8), 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Black Life, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Central Hall Artists, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Censorship, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Chemical Warfare, 1959-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Children/Childcare, 1954-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Chinatown, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Civil Rights, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Cities Decay, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Chrysler Corporation, 1955-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Congress, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 29)
- House: Republicans (Congress), undated; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Senate: Democrats (Congress), undated; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Counterrevolutionaries, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Color Purple Forum, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Demonstrations Death Penalty, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 34)
- House:Democrats (Congress), 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Dinkins Campaign, 1988-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Disabled, 1978-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Domestic History, 1915-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Draft, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Democrats, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Drugs, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Economy (U.S.) Budget, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Elderly, 1963-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Education/Daycare, 1977-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Elections, 1966-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Energy Not Nuclear see Nuke Energy, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 46)
- ERA, 1977-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Esmeralda, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Environment, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Peace Conferences, 1947-1952; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Pre-‘60s Anti-War Demonstrations & Protests, 1950-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Peace – 1967 Stockholm Sweden War Crimes Tribunal John Paul Sartre, Isaac Deutscher, etc., 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Various Demonstrations/Parades in NYC, 1953-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Housing, 1949-1970; 2.0 folders (Box 22, Folder 54-55)
- Ban the Bomb Demonstrations, 1957-1961; 2.0 folders (Box 22, Folder 56-57)
- South Africa – Demos/U.S., 1970-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 58)
- Third World Solidarity-Demonstrations, 1967-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 59)
- U.S. Demonstrations on Palestine, 1973-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Labor History, 1908-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Maritime Workers, 1948-1984; 6.0 folders (Box 23, Folder 41677)
- Labor – miscellaneous, 1963-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Lumberjacks, 1962-; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Machinists, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Mining – Copper/Zinc, 1950-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Labor:Miners, 1961-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Mine Workers, 1951-1978; 4.0 folders (Box 23, Folder 13-16)
- Mine Workers Pittston Strike Recent, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Mining Disasters, 1947-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Workers, 1956-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
- Newspaper Guilds, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Newspaper Workers, 1920-1989; 2.0 folders (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
- Paperworkers, 1987-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 24)
- PATCO/Hormel, 1966-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Postal Workers, 1955-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 26)